[SHAPE YOUR FUTURE]
[AI] [塑造你的未来]
Not too long ago. a mother told me.
[AI] 不久前，一位母亲告诉我，
“I can talk to my son in the dark.”
[AI] “我可以在黑暗中和我儿子说话。”
[Operator voice: The prepaid collect call from an inmate at --]
[AI] [接线员语音：囚犯拨打的预付对方付费电话--]
Her son was in prison
[AI] 她的儿子在监狱里
and paying for phone calls often meant she couldn't afford her light bill.
[AI] 支付电话费通常意味着她付不起小额账单。
See. families can pay as much as a dollar a minute
[AI] 你看，每个家庭每分钟可以付一美元
to speak to a loved one in prison or jail.
[AI] 在监狱或监狱里与所爱的人交谈。
These egregious rates
[AI] 这些惊人的比率
have created a 1.2-billion-dollar prison telecom industry
[AI] 创造了价值12亿美元的监狱电信产业
and with visit costs
[AI] 还有参观费
forced one in three families with an incarcerated loved one into debt.
[AI] 每三个家庭中就有一个被监禁的爱人负债累累。
Eighty-seven percent of those carrying this financial burden are women.
[AI] 承担这一经济负担的人中有87%是妇女。
And as a result of decades of racist policies and policing.
[AI] 由于几十年的种族主义政策和治安，
they're disproportionately Black and brown.
[AI] 它们是不成比例的黑色和棕色。
Prison telecom corporations claim that these high rates are necessary
[AI] 监狱电信公司声称这些高费率是必要的
to pay site commissions to prisons and jails
[AI] 向监狱和监狱支付现场佣金
and provide security and surveillance.
[AI] 并提供安全和监视。
While the government's hands are far from clean.
[AI] 虽然政府的手还很不干净，
these corporate claims are simply not supported by reality.
[AI] 这些公司的主张根本没有得到现实的支持。
Consider this.
[AI] 考虑一下这个。
In Connecticut.
[AI] 在康涅狄格州，
where families are charged as much as 32.5 cents per minute
[AI] 家庭收费高达每分钟32.5美分
and the state takes a 68 percent commission.
[AI] 州政府收取68%的佣金，
the telecom provider takes home 10 cents per minute.
[AI] 这家电信供应商每分钟赚10美分。
Now. in Illinois. where the state takes no commission.
[AI] 现在，在伊利诺伊州，该州不收取佣金，
families pay the same corporation nine tenths of a cent per minute.
[AI] 家庭每分钟向同一家公司支付十分之九美分。
In other words. even after the government takes its cut.
[AI] 换言之，即使在政府采取削减措施之后，
the corporation makes 10 times more in Connecticut than it does in Illinois
[AI] 该公司在康涅狄格州的收入是在伊利诺伊州的10倍
for providing the same service.
[AI] 提供同样的服务。
And prisons in Illinois are no less secure than those in Connecticut.
[AI] 伊利诺伊州的监狱也不亚于康涅狄格州的监狱。
These are simply corporate arguments
[AI] 这些只是公司的论点
used to justify predatory business practices
[AI] 用来证明掠夺性商业行为的正当性
and distract from the very simple truth.
[AI] 从简单的事实上转移注意力。
Corporations in the prison industry
[AI] 监狱行业的公司
have a financial interest in seeing more people behind bars
[AI] 看到更多的人坐牢有经济利益吗
and for longer periods of time.
[AI] 而且时间更长。
In reality. providing families and their incarcerated loved ones
[AI] 事实上，提供家庭及其被监禁的亲人
with regular communication
[AI] 定期沟通
is not just the right thing to do.
[AI] 这不仅仅是正确的做法。
It's also the most fiscally responsible and safe thing to do.
[AI] 这也是财政上最负责任和最安全的事情。
If you think taxpayers shouldn't be on the hook
[AI] 如果你认为纳税人不应该上钩
for phone calls for people who have committed crimes.
[AI] 给犯罪分子打电话，
remember this.
[AI] 记住这一点。
The most expensive rates are charged in jails
[AI] 监狱收取的费用最高
where the majority of people are awaiting trial and not yet convicted.
[AI] 大多数人正在等待审判，尚未被定罪。
Prison wages range from nothing to a few cents an hour.
[AI] 监狱的工资从零到每小时几美分不等，
so it's hard working. taxpaying families that are paying for calls.
[AI] 因此，为电话付费的是辛勤工作、纳税的家庭。
And maintaining strong community ties is one of the most important factors
[AI] 保持强大的社区联系是最重要的因素之一
in a person's successful reentry upon release.
[AI] 一个人获释后成功重返大气层。
It improves housing. employment and social outcomes.
[AI] 它改善了住房、就业和社会成果，
making it less likely that people need government support
[AI] 减少人们需要政府支持的可能性
or end up back in prison.
[AI] 或者回到监狱。
The bottom line is that prison telecom corporations.
[AI] 底线是监狱电信公司，
and the thousands of others in the prison industry.
[AI] 还有成千上万的监狱从业人员，
prioritize profit as they promote the caging of people
[AI] 优先考虑利润，因为利润促进了人员的集中
to exploit them and their families.
[AI] 剥削他们和他们的家人。
See. prison telecom is just one sector in the 80-billion-dollar prison industry.
[AI] 看，监狱电信只是价值800亿美元的监狱行业中的一个部门。
When I say prison industry.
[AI] 当我说监狱工业时，
I'm talking about food service corporations
[AI] 我说的是食品服务公司
that serve rotten meat to people behind bars.
[AI] 为监狱里的人提供腐肉，
health care providers that deny incarcerated people care.
[AI] 拒绝接受监禁人员护理的医疗保健提供者，
and architecture firms that design windowless six-by-nine-foot cells
[AI] 以及设计6×9英尺无窗单元的建筑公司
for solitary confinement.
[AI] 对于单独监禁，
where people spend weeks. months and even years.
[AI] 人们在那里度过数周、数月甚至数年。
We invest in these corporations
[AI] 我们投资这些公司
through our retirement funds. public pensions.
[AI] 通过我们的退休基金，公共养老金，
university endowments and private foundations.
[AI] 大学捐赠和私人基金会，
and we celebrate their executives
[AI] 我们为他们的高管们庆祝
on the boards of our favorite cultural institutions.
[AI] 在我们最喜欢的文化机构的董事会上。
And in all fairness. it's not just the private sector.
[AI] 平心而论，不仅仅是私营部门。
It's also government agencies that charge excessive fines and fees
[AI] 政府机构也会收取过高的罚款和费用
and abuse free or grossly underpaid prison labor
[AI] 以及无虐待或报酬极低的监狱劳动
to manufacture license plates.
[AI] 制造车牌.，
staff DMV call centers. fight wildfires
[AI] DMV呼叫中心工作人员，扑灭野火
and. yes. even pick cotton.
[AI] 是的，甚至可以摘棉花。
So this begs the question.
[AI] 这就引出了一个问题，
how can we address our crisis of mass incarceration
[AI] 我们如何解决大规模监禁的危机
if an entire segment of our economy is fighting to put more people behind bars
[AI] 如果我们整个经济领域都在努力把更多的人关进监狱
and for longer?
[AI] 还有更长的时间？
We can't.
[AI] 我们不能。
But we can demand and create change.
[AI] 但我们可以要求并创造变革。
The key is running coordinated policy and corporate campaigns.
[AI] 关键在于协调政策和企业活动。
That's the playbook I put to use when I founded Worth Rises.
[AI] 这是我在创立《沃斯崛起》时使用的剧本，
a nonprofit prison abolition organization
[AI] 非营利的废除监狱组织
dedicated to dismantling the prison industry.
[AI] 致力于拆除监狱行业。
Let's go back to prison telecom for a quick example.
[AI] 让我们回到监狱电信来举个简单的例子。
In 2018. we led a campaign in New York City
[AI] 2018年，我们在纽约市领导了一场运动
that passed the first piece of legislation to make jail phone calls free.
[AI] 通过了第一项免费监狱电话的立法，
saving families with incarcerated loved ones.
[AI] 拯救被监禁亲人的家庭，
nearly 10 million dollars a year
[AI] 每年将近1000万美元
and increasing communication by roughly 40 percent overnight.
[AI] 并在一夜之间增加了大约40%的沟通。
In 2019.
[AI] 2019年，
we helped local advocates in San Francisco introduce a similar policy
[AI] 我们帮助旧金山当地的倡导者引入了类似的政策。
and launched several statewide campaigns to do the same.
[AI] 并在全州范围内发起了几场类似的运动。
That same year.
[AI] 同年.，
we fought the consolidation of two major market players
[AI] 我们与两个主要市场参与者的合并进行了斗争
in front of the Federal Communications Commission and won.
[AI] 当着联邦通讯委员会的面赢了。
We blocked 150-million-dollar investment by a public pension
[AI] 我们通过公共养老金阻止了1.5亿美元的投资
with a private equity firm that owned a prison telecom corporation.
[AI] 一家私人股本公司拥有一家监狱电信公司。
And we removed one of the largest investors in the field
[AI] 我们删除了该领域最大的投资者之一
from a major museum board.
[AI] 来自一家大型博物馆的董事会。
In just two years.
[AI] 短短两年.，
we toxified the industry and threatened its business model.
[AI] 我们毒化了这个行业，威胁到它的商业模式，
causing an investor sell-off.
[AI] 导致投资者抛售。
But more importantly.
[AI] 但更重要的是，
that means millions of families connected
[AI] 这意味着数以百万计的家庭建立了联系
and billions of dollars protected
[AI] 数十亿美元得到保护
from the predatory hands of prison profiteers.
[AI] 从监狱奸商的掠夺之手。
It means fewer dollars invested in and promoting human caging and control.
[AI] 这意味着更少的资金投入和促进人类的囚禁和控制。
And it means at least one mother won't have to sit in the dark
[AI] 这意味着至少有一位母亲不必坐在黑暗中
to talk to her son again.
[AI] 再和她儿子谈谈。
[Operator: You may start the conversation now.]
[AI] [接线员：您现在可以开始通话了。]
Thank you.
[AI] 非常感谢。